NGUYEN HOANG NAM

Full stack Developer

Date of birth: 26/03/1996

Gender: Male

Phone:

Email:

Address: District 1, Ho Chi Minh City

OBJECTIVE

In my 6 years of programming experience, I have worked in various roles such as mobile, front-end, and back-end developer,

new domains and contribute to the long-term growth of the company.

, Sql Server, PostgreSQL, Elasticsearch, RabbitMQ, Html, Css, Js, Angular, Ionic, Jenkin, Jira, Redmine, SiemDC, Ranchers

In addition, I also possess skills such as: ReactJs, Flutter, MongoDB, NodeJS.

I want to learn, accumulate, share more experiences. I will do my best and become a key employee of the company for many years to come.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2017

Ho Chi Minh City Vocational College

Software applications

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2022-Now

SEN DO TECHNOLOGY JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Software Engineer

- Building warehouse management software for Sendo Farm
- Receiving and executing tasks under the direct guidance of the team leader
- Ensuring that the requirements and expectations of the management team are met within specified deadlines and with a high level of quality
- Monitoring the operational process during feature deployment to production, checking for errors, and troubleshooting issues when incidents occur

08/2021 - 05/2022

RENOVATION TECHNOLOGY

Software Engineer

- Building app and webite for cryptocurrency software on the blockchain platform.
- Receiving tasks from the leader.
- Participating in planning sessions to thoroughly understand project requirements
- Optimize speed and minimize errors occurring in production

03/2018 - 08/2021

DIGITAL SYSTEMS

Software Engineer

- Building app and web app transportation management software.
- Receiving and analyzing requests from customers
- Plan the construction for each module
- Build source code, setup CI/CD
- Assign tasks to the team
- Code
- Coordinate with stack holder for UAT plan, software deployment

09/2017 - 03/2018	VIETINFO TECHNOLOGY CORPORATION
	Fresher
	- Building apps Public Service Management Software.
	- Receiving tasks from the leader.
	- Research, build features for software.

SKILLS

Front-end	Html, Css Js, Angular
Back-end	.NET, NodeJs
Mobile	Ionic, React, Flutter
Database	SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Elasticsearch, MongoDB
Source Management	Github, Gitlab
Project Management	Jira, Redmine

PROJECTS

Warehoue Management Software (2022 - Now)

Customer	Sendo Farm
Description	- Web application for managing food raw materials, including tasks such as preprocessing, inventory checking, picking, reporting incidents, and handing over to stations
Team size	5
My position	Back-end Developer
My responsibilities	Receiving and executing tasks under the direct guidance of the team leader Ensuring that the requirements and expectations of the management team are met within specified deadlines and with a high level of quality Monitoring the operational process during feature deployment to production, checking for errors, and troubleshooting issues when incidents occur
Technologies used	Net Core MVC, Sql Server, PostgreSQL, Elasticsearch, RabbitMQ, Jenkin, Jira, SiemDC, Rancher

Buy/Sell NFTs on BlockChain network Software (2022 - 2022)

Customer	Product RNT
Description	- Website and App for customers to buy/sell NFTs
Team size	7
My position	Full stack Developer
My responsibilities	- Build features by documents - Research and development of features
Technologies used	- React, Flutter, NodeJS, MongoDB, Redmine

Buy/sell tokens and Participate in ICOs on the BlockChain network (2021 - 2022)

Customer	Product RNT
Description	- Website and App for customers to buy/sell tokens, participate in ICO, deposit/withdraw tokens.
Team size	7
My position	Full stack Developer
My responsibilities	- Build features by documents - Research and development of features
Technologies used	- React, Flutter, NodeJS, MongoDB, Redmine

Car Rental Software

(2020 - 2021)

Customer	Thanh Buoi
Description	- Website and App for customers to book a car, view prices, track booking status, pay,ment, report, statistics
Team size	5
My position	Full stack Developer, Leader
My responsibilities	 Receiving and analyzing requests from customers Plan the construction for each module Build source code, setup CI/CD Assign tasks to the team- Coding Coordinate with stack holder for UAT plan, software deployment
Technologies used	- Angular, .NET Core, Ionic, SQL Server, GitLab, Jira, Redmine

Logistics Software (2018 - 2021)

Customer	Thanh Buoi, Vietstar Express, GSDP, Nasco Express, Tasetco, Ship Nhanh, Flash Ship
Description	 Website and App for customers to create delivery requests, track orders, reports, statistics Website for employees to receive requests from customers, assign vehicles to pick up, transit, delivery, receive money, calculate salaries, report, statistics App for shipper to confirm pick-up points, transit, delivery, receive money from customer
Team size	5
My position	Full stack Developer, Leader
My responsibilities	 Receiving and analyzing requests from customers Plan the construction for each module Build source code, setup CI/CD Assign tasks to the team- Coding Coordinate with stack holder for UAT plan, software deployment
Technologies used	- Angular, .NET Core, Ionic, SQL Server, GitLab, Jira, Redmine